To sum up, there are four key points
that I want you to remember.
Firstly, note completion appears in section 4.
Secondly, you have to be well prepared for everything
before listening.
You need to read the requirement carefully.
Moreover, you have to predict what type of
information is missing from each blank based on
the context and grammar.
Thirdly, you always have to improve your vocabulary.
The first way is to learn topic related
vocabulary from the transcript after you finish each
listening section.
Another way is that you can listen to
TED talks or do exercises that prep designs
for you.
Finally, you have to be totally focused and
avoid being distracted when listening.
There are many times when you have to
base on the context, pronunciation and grammar to find
the answers.
So, let's study hard guys.
I hope you will achieve your desired score.
For now, goodbye and see you in the next lesson.